[](javascript:void(0))

Privacy Policy
==============

### Learn About Ryver Pricing

You are one step away from your 14 day Ryver Trial. Please tell us about yourself to get started.

* First Name\*
    
* Last Name\*
    
* Company Name\*
    
* Email\*
    
* Position/Title
    
* Country
    
    CountryAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCabo VerdeCambodiaCameroonCanadaCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongoCongo, Democratic Republic of theCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzechiaCôte d'IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatiniEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island and McDonald IslandsHoly SeeHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea, Democratic People's Republic ofKorea, Republic ofKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacaoMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth MacedoniaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaRéunionSaint BarthélemySaint Helena, Ascension and Tristan da CunhaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwedenSwitzerlandSyria Arab RepublicTaiwanTajikistanTanzania, the United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluTürkiyeUS Minor Outlying IslandsUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaViet NamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabweÅland Islands
    
* Phone Number\*
    
* How did you hear about us?\*
    
    *  LinkedIn Post
    *  Google/Search Engine
    *  iOS App Store
    *  Google Play Store
    *  
    
* Company Size\*
    
    *  1-50
    *  51-200
    *  201+
    
* 
* Comments
    
    This field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.

Δ

Close

**Last updated: January 7, 2019.**

Ryver LLC, a Delaware corporation (“Ryver” or “we” or “us” or “our”) is committed to the protection of your privacy. We have established this privacy statement (the ‘Statement’) as a means of disclosing to you how we collect, utilize, distribute, and protect your personal information. This privacy statement covers both the Site www.ryver.com (the “Site”) and the services and applications (the “Service”) that Ryver LLC provides. For the purposes of this Privacy Statement, “customer” shall mean any past, current, or prospective customer of Ryver, including any visitor to the Site. This Privacy Statement governs the manner in which Ryver collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from customers in connection with Ryver’s Site, services, and applications. Ryver is committed to safeguarding the information its customers entrust to it. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms of Service. By accessing or using the Service, you agree to this Privacy Statement.

#### Collecting and Using Information

Ryver uses information we collect to operate, maintain, and provide you the features and functionality of the Service, to analyze how the Service is used, diagnose service or technical problems, maintain security, personalize content, remember information to help you efficiently access your account, monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns, and track Content and users as necessary to comply with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act and other applicable laws.

**Organization Owners:** When a person signs up for a new Ryver organization, they are the Owner, or Primary Administrator, of that organization. As an Organization Owner, we may send you service, technical, and other administrative emails, messages, and other types of communications  in lieu of communication by postal mail. We may also contact you to inform you about changes in our Services, our Services offerings, and important Services-related notices, such as security and fraud notices. In addition, we may need to contact you for invoicing, account management, and similar reasons, and we use account data to administer accounts and keep track of billing and payments. These communications are considered part of the Services and you may not opt out of them. Finally, we sometimes send emails about new product features, promotional communications, or other news about Ryver, which you can opt out of receiving by unsubscribing via a link provided in the email or by writing to us at privacy@ryver.com.

**User Profiles:** When a Member or Guest is invited to a Ryver organization, they fill out a user profile, which includes an email address, display name, and other optional information. Ryver will use the email address for directly providing application services such as offline notifications. Additionally, we may use the email address to send tips on using the product. You can opt out of receiving these emails by unsubscribing via a link provided in the email or by writing to us at privacy@ryver.com.

**Error Log Data:** If you encounter an error in the Ryver application, we will provide a feedback form so you can report the problem to our customer support. The error report includes the operating system, browser, device information, and records the action that was being performed at the time the error occurred. This information is used to help diagnose and solve the customer problem.

**Third Party Service Integration:** Ryver connects to third party services such as Google Drive and Dropbox, to facilitate document attachments and Google Hangout integration. Ryver connects to these services via OAuth, and does not directly capture or store your username or password for these external services.

**Ryver Usage Metrics:** Ryver tracks application usage and stores it in a metrics database, from which we create charts and spreadsheets for analysis, allowing us to understand what parts of the Ryver service are and are not being used, and to what extent. Data tracked includes number of invites, number of teams created, number of chat messages, posts and comments, etc. This data does NOT include actual content such as team names, message content, or user names.

#### Content

**Your Content:** When you post content into Ryver, that content is private to you and the other users in your Ryver organization. Who exactly can see what content depends on the configuration of the teams and users in your organization.

**Ryver Employees:** We have taken steps at Ryver to ensure that your content remains private. While we are a technology company providing a service, and certain employees need to have access to customer data stores, we minimize that access, even amongst the engineering staff. By taking advantage of Amazon’s Identity and Access Management (IAM) configuration ([https://aws.amazon.com/iam/](https://aws.amazon.com/iam/)), we ensure that most of the Ryver employees are unable to access customer content data stores.

**Disclosure:** As outlined in section 5 (Acceptable User of Ryver) in the Ryver Terms of Service, there may be certain cases where Ryver is required to access, remove, preserve, or disclose information as necessary to comply with legal obligations and/or protect our users. As long as we are legally permitted, we will provide notice of any situation where accessing content becomes necessary. We will also request permission before accessing content to provide customer support.

#### Cookies and Log Files

When you use the Service, we may send one or more “cookies” (a small data file) to your computer to uniquely identify your browser and assist Ryver to help you log in faster and improve your navigation through the Site. A cookie may convey anonymous information to us about how you browse the Service. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser so that it can be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, certain features of the Service may not function properly if you disable the ability to accept cookies.

#### Device Identifiers and Geo-Location Information

Ryver does not currently collect precise GPS information with our mobile client. Should that change in the future, we will update our privacy policy, and take steps in the application to ensure that users are aware of such use of location information in order to provide our service. Should we add such a feature in the future, please note that a device identifier or location data does not collect or share any personally identifiable information about you.

#### Third Party Analytics

Ryver may use third party analytics tools, such as Google Analytics, to help understand use of the Service or the Ryver web site. Many of these tools collect the information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including cookies, and your IP address. These analytics tools also receive this information and their use of it is governed by their privacy policy or statement.

#### Third Party Website Remarketing

The Ryver web site may use third-party remarketing services to advertise on third-party websites (including Google, Facebook, and Twitter) to previous visitors to our site. These 3rd party sites use tracking cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our website. This means we might continue to show ads to you across the Internet, specifically on the Google Content Network (GCN), Facebook, and Twitter. As always, we respect your privacy, and we are not collecting any personally identifiable information through the use of Google’s, Facebook’s, Twitter’s, or any other 3rd party remarketing system. You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page ([http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/)). If you do not want Twitter to match your account to information shared by ad partners to tailor ads for you, you can uncheck the box next to “Promoted content” in your account settings at any time. (Read More ([https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405)) for details.) And, you can set preferences for how Facebook advertises to you by editing your privacy settings ([https://www.facebook.com/help/155389304528852](https://www.facebook.com/help/155389304528852)) on Facebook.

#### Protecting Information

Ryver makes diligent efforts to maintain accurate information on our customers. Ryver has put stringent security procedures in place to protect such information collected about our customers. We constantly monitor our systems, which are protected using industry-standard security measures. Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”) connections are used to communicate to our system to protect customer information as well as encrypting vital information that customers input through the Site. While Ryver cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be 100% secure, we take security very seriously and follow industry best practices. We have also paid for third party security audits in the past, and will continue to do so in the future.

#### Access to your personal data

We will display your personal identifiable information in your profile page and elsewhere on the Service according to the preferences you set for your user account. Any information you choose to provide should reflect how much you want others to know about you. Please carefully consider what information you disclose in your profile page and your desired level of anonymity. You can review and revise your profile information at any time by going to **_My Settings > Profile_**. We may also share or disclose your information with your consent, for example, if you use a third party application to access your account (see below). If you want to have your profile information completely removed (for example, after you leave a Ryver organization), please contact [privacyshield@ryver.com](http://privacyshield@ryver.com/) and we will delete your personal information completely from our system.

#### Service Providers and Third Party Services

Ryver may share your personally identifiable information or certain content with other third parties for the purpose of providing the Service to you. If we do this, such third parties’ use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Statement.

Ryver may share your information with a third party application with your consent, for example, when you choose to access our Service through such an application, and you provide that application with your Ryver login credentials. Ryver is not responsible for what those third parties do with your information, so you should make sure you trust the application and that it has a privacy policy or statement acceptable to you.

#### Business Transfers

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customers, email, and visitor information is generally one of the business assets transferred in these types of transactions. We may also transfer or assign such information in the course of corporate divestitures, consolidations, mergers, or dissolution.

#### Compliance with laws, law enforcement requests, and protection of Ryver

Ryver may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, law enforcement, or subpoena. Ryver may disclose your personal information if Ryver believes that it is reasonably necessary in order (i) to comply with law, regulation, or legal request; (ii) to protect the safety of any person; (iii) to address fraud, security, or technical issues; or (iv) to protect Ryver’s rights or property.

#### Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. Our Service is not directed to persons under 13. Ryver does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register with the Service. If we become aware that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will take steps to remove that information. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [feedback@ryver.com](mailto:feedback@ryver.com).

#### EU-US Privacy Shield Framework

Ryver complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States, respectively. Ryver has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/.

Ryver is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) with regard to the Privacy Shield Frameworks.

#### EU-US Privacy Complaints

In compliance with the US-EU Privacy Shield Principles, Ryver commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Jeff Hershauer at Ryver at privacyshield@ryver.com, or by mail at Ryver LLC, 9035 East Pima Center Parkway, Suite 5, Scottsdale, AZ 85258 USA.

Ryver has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism. If you are a resident of any European country that’s part of Privacy Shield and are not satisfied by our response to your grievance, you can seek independent recourse mechanism with EU Data Protection Authorities (DPA).

Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through these channels, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel.

#### EU GDPR

See **EU-US Privacy Shield Framework** and **EU-US Privacy Complaints** sections above, as well as our [GDPR page](https://ryver.com/gdpr/).

**Liability in case of onward transfer**

Ryver complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

#### Conditions of use and Concerns

By choosing to visit and interact with Ryver, customers agree that their visit and any dispute regarding the protection of their privacy during such visit is subject to this Privacy Statement including, but not limited to, the provisions regarding limitations on damages and the application of the law of the state of Delaware. Please note that if customers enter into other contractual agreements with Ryver, privacy terms and conditions of such other agreements may supplement or supersede this policy. Questions and concerns about privacy at Ryver should be directed to [feedback@ryver.com](mailto:feedback@ryver.com).

By Mail:  
Ryver LLC  
9035 East Pima Center Parkway, Suite 5  
Scottsdale, AZ 85258  

**Changes to Ryver’s Privacy Statement**

Ryver reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement and other policies prospectively at any time, subject to applicable laws and regulations, by posting notice of such changes on the Site. Regardless of later updates or changes to our Privacy Statement, we will never use the information you submit under our current Privacy Statement in a new way without first providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent that use. In such an event of a material change, we shall notify you by email, or a prominent notice on the Site.

##### Why Ryver

##### Solutions

##### Company

##### Resources

© Ryver, Inc. All rights reserved.
